geekword.net 2013-11-27

# Privacy Policy | Geekword

Geekword highly values and appreciates your readership and your privacy matters are of extreme importance to us. Before going into the details, we will like you to know that the personal information collected by us is always kept confidential and will never be sold to third parties. This privacy policy document covers the points regarding personal information received and collected by us and also how much secure you are by visiting Geekword.

**Log Files**

****Like many other Web portals, Geekword makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browsers, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, number of clicks to analyze trends & administer the site, track user’s movement around the website, and also gather demographic info of the users visiting.

IP addresses, and other similar information is not linked to any details that is personally identifiable.

**Cookies and Web Beacons**

****http://www.geekword.net does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, it record user-specific information i.e which pages were accessed or visited by the user, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

**DoubleClick DART Cookie**

****Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on Geekword. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit at http://www.geekword.net and other websites. You may opt out the use of DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL – http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site:

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology (send directly to your browsers) in the advertisements and links that appears on http://www.geekword.net. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

We have no access and control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.  You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. Geekword.net’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such third-party advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.

**Comment Policy:**

a) Information we receive through comments:

Commenting on geekword is intensely safe, because whenever you post a comment on any article of geekword, we receive information i.e your name, email address and ip address. This acquired information only stays with us and will never be disclose to any third-party.

b) Comment Moderation:

Geekword is not responsible for the disclosure of your personal information by yourself in any comment you post. Geekword applies the method of comment moderation, the moderation is done on regular intervals i.e whenever the comment is posted on any article. Comments having foul language, personal attacks, spam and off-topic will not be approved.

_Changes in Privacy Policy:_  
_This privacy policy is not fixed and may get update from time to time, so we encourage our users to visit the privacy policy page periodically in order to get updated from the revised version of our privacy policies._

**Contact Us:**

****If you require further information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by emailing at[contact@geekword.net](mailto:contact@geekword.net)
